位于华府附近的帕塔克森特河海军航空站
Patuxent River Naval Air Station near DC.,
在约翰·麦凯恩祖父的主持下
was commissioned in 1943
于1943年正式启用
by John McCain's grandfather.
我在考虑去玩滑翔翼
I'm thinking of going hang gliding.
帕塔克河上的气流相当平缓
Pax River is, like, completely flat.
我想这正是V-22鱼鹰式倾转旋翼机
Think that's why they tested
V-22鱼鹰式倾转旋翼机
兼具直升机和固定翼螺旋桨飞机的优点
选在那里试飞的原因
the V-22 Osprey there.
我喜欢研究海军装备
I like naval stuff.
我喜欢他们的橙子  和皮棉衣
I like their oranges and lint.
什么病不是肾病却神似肾病
What looks ike kidney disease, but isn't.
奇斯哪去了
And where is Chase?
去看牙根管  还有比格氏病
Root canal and Berger's.
第一个是说奇斯
The first one was regarding Chase,
他去治牙根管
root canal.
如果治疗得当  就不像肾病了
If done correctly, it doesn't look like kidney disease.
给你找了个病人
Got a case for you.
好像挺有意思
Smells funny.
病人突发特发性过敏反应
Patient had an idiopathic anaphylactic reaction.
难倒了两名急诊室医生
It stumped two E.R. docs,
还有一位约翰·霍普金斯大学的免疫学家
and an immunologist from Johns Hopkins.
在一年之内  患者从无症状到
Patient went from asymptomatic to fried kidneys
肾功能衰竭
in less than a year.
难倒了三位内科医师
Stumped three internists
和一个哈佛的科室主任
and a department chair from Harvard.
十四岁的女孩  间歇性发作
14-year-old girl, intermittent attacks.
四岁的小男孩  一直在鬼门关徘徊
Four-year-old boy, consistently at death's door.
这病人五年前就死了
This patient died five years ago.
我又没说他在门里还是门外
I didn't say which side of the door he was on.
他的死亡让这病例更有趣
The fact that he's dead makes it more interesting.
四岁的孩子是不会死于比格氏病的
Four-year-olds do not die of Berger's.
我以为这是有关的
I thought it was relevant.
死亡是结果  而不是症状
Death is a consequence, not a symptom.
只要它不是症状  就没有关系
If it's not a symptom, it's not relevant.
我们是不是该试着尽力
Shouldn't we be trying to maximize
拯救可以挽救的东西呢
what we can save here,
比如十四岁女孩的生命  你的自由和我们的生计
14-year-old, your freedom, our asses?
好吧  努力自保吧
Right... save your asses.
总监：
zlean
她两岁时出过车祸
She was in a car accident when she was two.
她只受了些轻伤  但她父亲死了
She only had minor injuries, but her father died.
那是十二年前的事了  你认为这有关吗
That was 12 years ago. You think that's pertinent?
不  我认为她挺可怜的
No, I think it's sad.
她在十四岁生日聚会上生病了
She got sick in the middle of her 14th birthday party,
这既可怜而又相关
which is sad and pertinent.
或许她当时正在打开一份礼物
Maybe she was opening a present
才引发了过敏反应
that triggered the reaction.
-豪斯人呢  -跟福曼比吹胡子瞪眼
- Where's House? - Pissing contest with Foreman.
她最后吃的东西是草莓蛋糕
Last thing she ate was strawberry cake,
但是过敏原检测显示她对什么都不过敏
but allergy tests for everything were negative.
你喜欢你的牙医吗
Do you like your dentist?
我现在找的还是我小时候看牙的医生
I'm still going to my pediatric one.
你牙医叫什么
What's your dentist's name?
-威廉姆斯  -如果不是过敏反应呢
- Williams. - What if it's not an allergic reaction?
遗传性血管水肿
Hereditary angioedema
或是全身性肥大细胞增多症
or systemic mastocytosis
可能表现为过敏反应
could mimic anaphylaxis.
你不太清楚他的名字吗
You're not sure of his name?
你今天早上才去看的牙医
You just saw him this morning.
他的助手叫安吉
His assistant's name is Angie.
她家电话是...
Her home number is--
防御素检测值正常
Normal complement studies
没有皮肤损害
no skin lesions.
你去修指甲了
You had a manicure.
这是刚修剪过的  你没去看牙医
This is fresh! You weren't at the dentist.
你为什么要说谎呢
Why would you lie about that?
就是不想有人多问
To avoid having this conversation.
血压高  会不会是嗜铬细胞瘤
Elevated bp. What about pheochromocytoma?
或者就是过敏反应
Or an anaphylactoid reaction,
可能由某些鸦片类药剂引起
which could be triggered by certain opioids.
自我认识你以来  你剪过三次头发
You've had your hair cut three times since I've met you.
你不可能为修指甲而不好意思
You can't be embarrassed about a manicure.
肯定有更深层次的原因
There's gotta be a deeper reason.
是不是豪斯让你问的
Did House give you homework?
她什么药都没吃过
She's not on any meds.
你没听说过吗  所有人都会说谎
Haven't you heard? Everybody lies.
毒理检验未检出毒物
And the tox screen was clean.
你们俩随时可以发表意见
Feel free to jump in at any time.
我们会检测血儿茶酚胺以确定有无嗜铬细胞瘤
We'll check catecholamines for pheo
然后再做次扩展鸦片筛检
and run an expanded opioid panel.
你们趁她母亲没在病房时
You see what the patient says about drug use
再问问她吸毒的事
when her mother's out of the room.
没有  从没吸过
No, never.
我们不是想揭发你  艾瑞斯
Nobody's here to bust you, Iris.
我们只需要知道你是否...
We just need to know if--
没有  我已经告诉过你们了
No, I already told you.
我就有时吃点维生素C
I just take vitamin C sometimes.
当你发病时  你具体在干什么
What exactly were you doing when you had your reaction?
拆一件生日礼物  是魔力八号球
Opening a birthday present, the magic 8 ball.
是开玩笑的玩具  不是可卡因
The joke gift, not the cocaine.
行了吗
Is that it?
有些药物可以引起她的过敏反应
Certain drugs could explain her reaction.
哪些药物
What kind of drugs?
你能想到什么
What kind did you have in mind?
艾瑞斯一直是一个情绪化的女孩
Iris has always been a moody girl.
现在她到了青春期  就更严重了
And now that she's a teenager, it's gotten worse.
所以这几个月来
So for the past few months I've been...
我一直给她吃些药  想让她放松些
giving something to relax her.
安定  我告诉她是维生素C
Diazepam. I tell her it's vitamin c.
艾瑞斯很想做个正常的女孩
Being normal is very important to Iris.
她会无法接受自己需要长期服药的事实
She couldn't handle the thought of being on meds.
抗焦虑药能引起这种反应
Anti-anxiety medications would explain it.
如果我们停止用这药
If we keep her off,
她会情绪化  但是会很健康
she'll be moody, but healthy.
或者另有病因
Or it's something else.
我需要和你一起为一个病人做会诊
I need to DDX a patient with you.
你不是有个干这活的团队吗
I thought you had a team for that.
根据福曼的说法
According to Foreman,
他们只能用来给活人做会诊
they're only for DDXing people who are still alive.
你有一个死病人吗
You have a dead patient?
修饰偏见很是无聊
Bigotry is boring when we add modifiers.
我不去过问他的信仰  肤色  有没有脉搏
I don't see creed, color, pulse.
福曼会发现你在研究这病例
Foreman will find out you're taking this case,
他会告发你
and he'll bust you.
但这你知道
But you know that,
也就是说
which means...
你想回监狱
You want to go back to jail...
因为只有那里
Because it's the one place
容不得你沉溺于自我毁灭的习惯
you're unable to indulge your self-destructive habits.
是啊  我接这个病例更有可能
Yeah, it's much more likely that I'm taking this case
是因为我怀念囹圄时光
because I miss showering with cro-magnons
而不是我真的觉得它有趣
than that I actually happen to find it interesting.
四岁大的孩子
Four-year-old kid.
先是肾脏衰竭  他们给他输血
His kidneys died, they transfused.
接着又肺衰竭  他就死了
His lungs died. He died.
看过《魔鬼新娘》没有
Have you seen Bride Of The Monster?
我刚买到艾德·伍德电影集锦
I just got the Ed wood box set.
会不会搞错顺序
What if the chicken was the egg?
如果是肺部先出的问题呢
What if the lung involvement came first?
其实我不怎么在乎那部电影
I don't really care about the movie.
-我只是不想纵容你的...  -红斑狼疮
- I just don't want to indulge your- - Lupus.
因为这样做没有好下场  豪斯
Because this is a bad idea, House.
如果这孩子有皮疹
If the kid had a rash
或有些循环问题
or some circulation issue...
该死
Damn!
我才发觉我愤怒控制课要去晚了
I just realized I'm late for my anger management class.
交通  当然是一大问题
Traffic, for sure.
税收  无疑也是
Taxes. Definitely taxes.
被宠坏的孙子孙女
Spoiled grandchildren.
俗
Platitudes.
还有其它的吗
Any others?
我有时发脾气是因为有人说
And I lose my temper when someone suggests
几句大众心理学的口头禅
that a handful of pop-psych catch phrases
就能控制住我们最重要的  最难以控制的
can control our most seminal, intractable,
也是最自然的  对痛失爱子的反应
and natural reaction to a dead child.
我说得对吗  埃莫雷
Am I right, Emory?
我觉得埃莫雷现在不想分享
I don't think Emory wants to share right now.
他们搞砸了  对吧
They blew it, didn't they?
他们没留意到你儿子的皮疹
They missed your son's rash.
不很明显  在他脖子上
A faint one, on his cheek.
他没有皮疹
He didn't have a rash.
我认为我们该聊聊莉娜的孙子  孙女
I think we should talk about Lena's grandchildren.
他们活着
They're alive.
-他对阳光敏感吗  -不
- Was he sensitive to sunlight? - No.
-格雷戈  -手脚冰凉吗
- Greg... - Cold fingers and toes?
不
No!
韦格纳肉芽肿
Wegener's granulomatosis.
我需要给你儿子做检查
I need to examine your son.
有点晚了  混蛋
You're a bit late for that...you ass.
只要你和你妻子同意
With you and your wife's consent,
我们就能获准开棺验尸
we can get an exhumation order.
找出他的死因
Find out what killed him.
是前妻
Ex-wife.
而且她永远不会同意
And you'll never get her consent.
她已开始新生活  新丈夫  新孩子
She's moved on-- new hub, new kid.
她不想再跟德鲁的死有任何瓜葛
She wants nothing to do with Drew's death.
对我也是
Or me.
你愤怒是因为你儿子死了
You're angry because your kid died.
不仅如此
More than that,
更因为你还不知道死因
because you don't have an answer.
人们总想讨个说法
People need answers.
他葬在圣犹达公墓的一个墓室里
He's in a crypt at St. Jude's cemetery.
这里有疼痛感吗
You feeling any pain or cramping here?
一点点
A bit.
但不止那里
But not just there, um...
这也有
Here.
乳房触痛
Breast tenderness.
你经期正常吗  艾瑞斯
Have you been having regular periods, Iris?
不太好
Not really.
怎么了
What is it?
我觉得我们应该验孕
I think we should run a pregnancy test.
艾瑞斯没有性行为
Iris isn't sexually active.
她都没有男朋友
She doesn't even have a boyfriend.
怀孕能解释所有症状
Pregnancy would explain all of her symptoms.
甚至是引起不可预知的过敏反应
Can even cause some unpredictable allergic reactions.
我都没性行为怎么会怀孕呢
How can I be pregnant if I've never even had sex?
我们只需抽点血
We just need a drop of blood.
怎么了
What's the matter?
我的
My--
我的手臂
my arms.
失去知觉了
I can't feel my arms.
照这么个速度
At this rate,
我就得给自己找块墓地了
I'm gonna need to pick out a plot for myself.
鉴于你的慷慨捐赠
Thanks to your generous donation,
你可以待一早上
you have all morning.
我看就剩十三分钟了
More like 13 minutes.
在进去之前  医生
Before we proceed any further, doctor,
我要问你具体打算
I'd like inquire as to exactly what procedure
对遗体做些什么
you intend to perform on the remains.
你听说过
Have you ever heard of
北美男人与死童关爱协会吗
the North American Man/Dead Boy Love Association?
这里在我眼中是个神圣的地方
I consider these grounds to be a holy place,
我得要求你礼待逝者
and I would ask you to observe them with due decorum.
你拿红包放盗墓的进去
So you're taking bribes to plunder graves,
我却要尊重死者
and I need to show respect.
我认为他们错判了死因
I think they got the cause of death wrong.
如果我在他的鼻软骨上找到一个洞
And if I find a hole in the cartilage of his nose,
就在这
right about here,
就意味着我是对的
then it means I'm right.
请放尊重些
Please be respectful.
石棺已经帮你开好了
I prepared the sarcophagus for you.
谢谢  伊戈尔
Thank you, Igor.
我叫米尔顿
It's Milton.
尿都被你吓出来了
You owe me a new pair of pants.
她怀孕了  结果呈阳性
She is pregnant. Test came back positive.
所以  她不止失了双臂活动能力
So...she lost the use of her arms
还丢了贞节
and her innocence.
遭天谴吗
A vengeful god?
还是...
Or...
脑瘤
Cerebral tumor.
血管炎
Vasculitis.
多发性硬化
MS.
从此刻的寂静推断
I gather from the silence
奇斯不在
that Chase isn't there.
错了  我就在这
Nope, I'm here.
你在哪
Where are you?
"哪都不在"
"Nowhere"...
他神秘兮兮地说
He said cryptically.
我想你赞同他们的诊断吧
I assume you concur with the diagnosis.
必须的
Absolutely.
同意他们的三种诊断吗
Even though there are three diagnoses?
还有  多发性硬化和血管炎
And MS and vasculitis
在怀孕之后通常都会出现好转
usually get better with pregnancy.
我是说我完全同意另一个观点
Yeah, I was saying I agreed with the other one.
他居然修过眉毛了
He's had his eyebrows waxed.
我正在约会的女孩喜欢男人修整得干干净净
I met a woman who likes her men well groomed.
浑身上下吗
All over?
从此刻的寂静推断
I assume, from the silence,
奇斯做了个泳装除毛
that Chase has had a Brazilian.
-不错啊  -有意思
- Cool. - Interesting.
蛋疼啊
Ouch.
问题就在于  真的只是因为女人
Question is... is this really about a woman?
还是有什么深层原因
or is it about something more profound?
另一个问题是  她的感觉异常
Another question is, could the paresthesia
有没有可能是性病引起的
be caused by an STD?
HIV相关性多发性单神经炎
HIV-related mononeuritis multiplex.
从此刻的寂静推断
I gather from the silence
要么你们都赞同奇斯的观点
that either you all agree with Chase
要么就是在盯着他伪娘的眉毛
or you're just staring at his emasculated brow.
不管怎么着  先做个HIV病毒检测
In either case, test for HIV
再做个核磁共振看看是不是肿瘤
and do an MRI to rule out tumors.
顺便检查一下奇斯的睾丸激素
And check Chase for testosterone.
HIV血液测试呈阴性
Blood work was negative for HIV.
只能押宝在肿瘤上了
All the money's on tumor.
泳装除毛感觉如何啊
How was the Brazilian?
还行  就是有点疼
It was fine. Hurt a bit.
那豪斯的理论呢
What about House's theory?
你到底是为什么做那玩意
Why'd you really do it?
因为我又虚荣又浅薄
cause I'm vain and shallow.
你以前就不是了吗
And you weren't before?
我以前约会的女孩不看重这些
The girl I was seeing wasn't.
没什么秘密好挖的
There's nothing profound here.
也不是肿瘤
No tumor, either.
她的大脑没问题
It's not her brain.
一切正常
Everything looks good.
你怎么了
What's the matter?
我的手臂...
My arm, it's...
还是什么感觉都没有吗
Still nothing?
不是  很酸
No, now they're sore.
感觉失常的症状消失了
Paresthesia's gone.
瘀伤会不会是身体创伤留下的
Could the bruising be caused by a physical trauma?
那她得从床上摔下来多少次才能变成那样
You think she fell out of bed, repeatedly?
血液疾病  可能是血小板减少症
A blood disorder. Maybe thrombocytopenia.
维生素K缺乏症或者败血症
A vitamin k deficiency or scurvy
可以解释她的出血
could explain bleeding problems,
怀孕又会加重这个症状
and pregnancy could exacerbate it.
带把的去搜家  不带的去做检查
Boys, do a home search. Girls, do lab tests.
我很确定这不算性别歧视
I'm pretty sure that's not sexist.
你去哪了
Where have you been?
取了趟干净衣服
Picking up dry cleaning.
加了个油
Filling up the tank.
奸了个尸
Violating the dead.
不信的话打电话去监控公司问问
If you don't believe me, call the monitoring company.
我问过了
I did.
不幸的是  帕塔克森特河海军航空站
Unfortunately, the Patuxent river naval air station
正好在进行卫星定位测试  干扰了信号
was GPS testing and disrupted the signal,
而且就刚好是你不在的那45分钟
at the exact, same 45 minutes you weren't here.
要是我知道我有45分钟的自由活动时间
Well, if I'd known I had 45 minutes of freedom,
我就去玩滑翔翼了
I'd have gone hang gliding.
这点子我喜欢
I admire the creativity.
但你有没有想过要是干扰没起作用的话怎么办
But what happens when the stunt doesn't work?
你以为后果就是你认赌服输
Think you're gonna have to pay off a bet?
我罚你三倍门诊时间了事吗
Think I'm gonna triple your clinic hours?
我会打电话给你的假释官
I'm gonna call your P.O.,
把你送回牢里去
and you're gonna go back to jail.
他的指甲盖上有米氏线
There are Mees' lines on his fingernails,
我现在怀疑他是重金属中毒
so now I'm thinking heavy metal poisoning.
你是个瘾君子
You're an addict.
而我蠢到以为你只对
And I'm an idiot for thinking that your addictions
药物  反社会行为和冷嘲热讽上瘾
were limited to pills, anti-social behavior, and sarcasm.
不好意思
Sorry.
维柯丁放不下我
Vicodin repeating on me.
让你上瘾的还有谜题
You're also addicted to puzzles.
你表现出全部的典型症状
You show all the classic behaviors.
说谎  不负责任
Lying, neglecting responsibilities,
而且不管后果多严重你都没有办法收手
and you can't stop, no matter how devastating the consequences.
解决病例又没有违反保释条例
Working on a medical case is not a parole violation.
是我该做的
It's my job description.
你该做的是对福曼言听计从
Your job description is doing what Foreman tells you to do.
别管什么《魔鬼新娘》了
Never mind Bride of the Monster.
你真该好好看看《诺玛·蕊》
You need to watch Norma Rae.
在我们开始之前
Before we get started,
感谢大家愿意移驾到此
I just want to thank you all for agreeing to relocate.
我之前在这附近有个约会
Um, I had an appointment in this part of town,
但是我也不想错过和大家的聚会
and I absolutely didn't want to miss this meeting.
不管怎么说  谢谢你们
But, uh, thank you.
这顿我买单
I'm buying.
大家别当真
Not literally.
埃莫雷
Hey, Emory,
我们一起去趟洗手间吧
should we, uh, powder our noses?
问你啊  你知不知道你前妻
Hey, did you know your ex-wife
还住在这栋房子后面
still lives right behind this place?
她四点下班
She finishes work at 4:00.
四点一刻去接她的二儿子
Picks up her new kid at 4:15.
我们有二十分钟左右时间
Gives us about 20 minutes.
我打过几次电话
I made some calls.
如果你问得够霸气  对方会出乎意料的坦诚
It's amazing what people will tell you if you ask brutally enough.
是这张桌子吗
Was that table here?
一些经过压力处理的木材可能含砷
Some kinds of pressure-treated wood can contain arsenic.
我们不该来的
We shouldn't be here.
我们别无选择
We don't have a choice.
这是你唯一能找到答案的办法
This is the only way you're gonna get your answer.
知道你前妻把备用钥匙藏在哪吗
Does your ex leave a spare key anywhere?
他看上去怎么样
How did he look?
很安详
Peaceful.
缺乏维生素K看来是不可能了
Vitamin K deficiency's a bust.
冰箱里的菠菜和西兰花
Fridge has more spinach and broccoli
比菜场的还多
than a farmer's market.
泳装除毛
The brazilian...
你说"有点疼"
You said it hurt "a bit."
你做过吗
You've had one?
不止一次  而你没有
More than one, and you haven't.
那是相当得疼
They hurt all your bits.
那是我不为人知的小秘密
That's my dark secret.
你的呢
What's yours?
我做了指甲和眉毛
I had the nails and eyebrows done,
仅此而已
but that's it.
我只是要分散你们的注意力
I just needed to create a distraction, though.
有次吃饭我碰到一个电视制作人
I met a TV producer at a dinner.
她让我上一个医务节目
She asked me to appear on the medical segment.
昨天试镜  今天拍摄
Screen tested it yesterday and shot it today.
你做电视医生了吗
You're a TV doctor?
就一次
It's a one-off.
什么时候播
When's it air?
两小时以前
Two hours ago.
不然  我现在也不会告诉你
Otherwise, I'd still be lying.
她就是在打开这个的时候突然发病的
This is what she was opening when she had her attack.
会有人信奇斯真的是医生吗
Will anyone believe Chase is an actual doctor?
"做梦吧"
"Don't count on it."
她的确有男朋友
She does have a boyfriend.
情书
Love letters.
-黄片  -还挺重口
- Porn. - The nasty kind.
折磨  强奸  动物
Torture, rape... animals.
好一个乖孩子
Sweet kid.
只剩这些了
This is all that's left.
柜子底下的一个小盒子
One box in the bottom of a closet.
他以前总喜欢戴这些小东西
He used to wear those stupid things all the time.
我总要假装被他吓到
Used to have to pretend I was scared.
铅涂料人民共和国制造
Made in the People's Republic of Lead Paint.
后门
Back door.
我们先离开再说吧
Let's get out of here first.
再不回去互助会要结束了
We need to catch the end of our class.
我在学校认识他的
I met him at school.
他是唯一一个喜欢我的男孩
He was the only boy that liked me.
这不只是喜欢了
It's a little more than like.
我们没有发生关系
We haven't had sex.
拜托  艾瑞斯  你都怀孕了
Oh, come on, Iris. You're pregnant.
那我说的就都是假的了吗
So I'm just lying about everything?
你骗我说没有男朋友
Well, you lied about the boyfriend.
没有发生关系显然也是骗人的
You obviously lied about sex
还有这些  垃圾
And this...garbage.
是他的
They're his.
他家没法放
He can't keep them at his place.
我们这么随和真太好了
Well, I'm glad we could be so accommodating.
还有什么我不知道的
What else don't I know?
亲爱的
Honey...
怎么了
What is it?
他昨天晚上来过
He came here last night.
他说我应该离开
And he told me I should leave.
但我不想  他就生气了
But I didn't want to, and he got mad.
他打你了
He hit you?
身体创伤
Physical trauma.
所以血液疾病检测呈阴性
Explains the negatives of the blood disorder.
我们应该报警
We should call the police.
我什么都不会说的
I won't tell them anything.
太荒谬了
That's ridiculous.
他打你
He beat you!
怎么了
What is it?
我看不清了
It's getting hard to see.
我到底怎么了
What the hell is happening to me?
外用酒精  醋
Rubbing alcohol, vinegar.
不清楚这是啥
Not sure what this is.
不能做正规的医疗测试吗
Aren't there actual medical tests?
死去的患者一般只能享受低水准的服务
Dead patients usually get a lower standard of care.
粉红色代表铅中毒
Pink means lead.
橘红色代表汞中毒
Orange means mercury.
铁锈色代表砷中毒
And rust means arsenic.
棕色呢
And what's brown mean?
苏格兰威士忌
Scotch.
他以前叫它"梆梆"
He used to call him "deezer."
因为他不会说"斑马"
He couldn't say "zebra."
他给所有东西都重新起了名
He'd have his own words for everything.
我们管这叫"德氏物语"
We called 'em "Drewisms."
你的前妻是怎么做到的
How does your ex-wife do it?
她怎么就不...愤怒和痛苦
How come she's not... angry and miserable?
她就当什么都没发生过似的
She treated it like it never happened.
一次都没哭过
She never even cried.
连葬礼上也没有
Not even at his funeral.
我哭得稀里哗啦的
I was a mess,
她只是坐在那  就像是...
and she just sat there like...
一尊雕塑
a statue.
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
这麻烦跛脚吗
Does it limp?
你为什么不让他同时接两个病例
Why do you care if he works on two cases?
因为之后  他就会接三个  然后四个
'cause next, it'll be three cases, then four.
然后动物的  然后鬼魂的
Then animal cases and ghost cases.
然后动物的鬼魂的
Then animal ghost cases.
当然  如果我们是在说豪斯的话
Assuming, of course, we are talking about House.
你铁定得输
You're just setting yourself up to fail.
但他输不起  他明白的
He has a lot more to lose than I do, and he knows that.
他很理性的
He's rational.
他才不是呢
No, he's not.
他是我见过的最理性的人
He's the most rational man I've ever met.
理性到烦人
Annoyingly so.
他不会为了一个死了的孩子把自己送回监狱的
He isn't gonna put himself back in jail over a dead kid.
他是个瘾君子
He's an addict,
为了解谜  他宁愿把自己送回监狱
and he will put himself back in jail over a puzzle.
他会罢手的
He'll back down.
视野检查过程中
Halfway through the perimetry exam,
她的管状视野消失了
her tunnel vision went away.
-她的视力恢复了  -短暂性缺血发作
- She can see perfectly. - TIA.
发病时期短  病如其名
The word "transient" is right there in the name.
不是吧
Ah, here we go.
蔡莎  看过你的照片后
Chesa, after giving the pics an eye or two,
我敢肯定劳伦为了她的手术花了不少银子
I can confirm that Lauren's surgeries cost her some big bikkies.
除了缩胃术
Not only was there a gut tuck,
隆鼻  还有丰臀
nose tuck, and arse tuck,
但她的新假胸就如狗鞭般直指九天
but her new, fake norks stick out like nuts on a mutt.
原本的台词是
The original script was--
有人注意到...
Anyone notice...
有如醍醐灌顶啊
He's enlightening us.
因为他还给老二美了容
That's cause he's retooled the ol' todger.
希望他没剪到不该剪的
Let's just hope no one cut the wrong wire, eh?
原来你只是希望在电视上显得帅点儿
So you just wanted to look pretty on TV.
问题是  他为什么想要这样呢
Question is, why did he want that?
门诊时间到
Clinic time.
你想让我们做什么呢
What do you want us to do?
用脑血管造影查短暂性缺血发作
MRA for TIA.
顺便笑得满地打滚
ROFL.
你不是只有周二才有门诊吗
Thought you only had clinic on Tuesdays.
没错
Oh, you're right.
你好  我是来注射免费流感疫苗的
Hi. I'm here for the free flu shot.
我接到电话说...
I got a call saying--
我是来弄清楚你为什么
I'm here to find out why
不关心自己的第一个孩子
you didn't care about your first kid.
痛失爱子  你却能轻松面对
Losing a child-- Just breezed right through it.
你怎么知道我第一个孩子...
How do you know about my first kid--
甚至在葬礼上都没有掉一滴眼泪
Didn't even squeeze out a single tear at the funeral.
你到底想说什么
Where are you getting this?
你立马就生了第二胎来替代他
You couldn't wait to squeeze out a brand-new replacement kid.
该死
Damn it.
你没有权利这么说
You had no right to say that.
我知道  我就是找抽
I know. I deserved the slap.
但我本希望你就是不会愤怒
But I was hoping that you weren't capable of it.
淡漠型甲状腺机能亢进
Apathetic hyperthyroidism.
可能是肾脏引起的  或是与基因有关
Could have kidney involvement. Could be genetic.
一定会引起冷漠反应
Definitely causes apathy.
我本指望你的冷漠
I was hoping that your lack of emotion
是你遗传给你第一个儿子的
was a symptom of something you could
一种症状呢
have passed on to your first son.
你认识埃莫雷
You know Emory.
我们是同一家俱乐部的
We belong to the same club.
他想再经历这一切
He wants to relive this.
我不想
I don't.
我听说了
So I heard.
埃莫雷是个好男人
Emory was a wonderful man.
从不惧于展现自己的情感
Never afraid to show his emotions.
大多数情况下  这很好
Which is great, most of the time.
但德鲁死后...
But when Drew died...
他悲痛不能自已
It overwhelmed him.
我发誓不会像他一样
I vowed I wouldn't let that happen to me.
这就是你离开他的原因吗
That's why you left him?
我离开是因为他的眼睛
I left because of his eyes.
和德鲁一模一样
He had Drew's eyes.
以前是谁照看德鲁的
Who used to babysit Drew?
我父亲  但...
My father, but--
在他家还是你家
His place or yours?
有两种人
There are two types of people.
有些人迎接新生活  有些人沉溺于往事
Those who can move on, and those who can't.
我父亲外表看来已经释然了
My father keeps up a good front,
但其实他和埃莫雷一样
but he's just like Emory.
别去烦他
You need to leave him alone.
这就是说他有双重人格
So he has two types of people inside of him.
脑血管造影检查没有异常
MRA was normal.
没错  你怎么...
Yeah, how did--
我找到你男友住的地方了
I found out where your boyfriend lives.
我去拜访他的时候  他跑了
When I paid him a visit, he took off.
被一辆车撞了
Ran in front of a car.
你在撒谎
You're lying.
他正在楼下的急救室呢
He's down in the E.R. right now.
闭嘴  你个臭骗子
Shut up, you lying sack of crap.
艾瑞斯
Iris!
你怎么知道我在撒谎呢
How do you know I'm lying?
你怎么知道你男友没事呢
How do you know your boyfriend's okay?
因为我就在这儿呢  混蛋
Cause I'm right here, you dick.
艾瑞斯有分离性身份识别障碍
Iris has dissociative identity disorder.
也就是多重人格障碍
Also known as multiple personality disorder.
你是说我疯了吗
Are you saying I'm crazy?
这是大脑对严重外伤的反应
It's the mind's response to a severe trauma.
当人们经历了难以接受的事情
A person experiences something that's too difficult to accept,
他们会创造出另一个不用接受现实的人格
so they create alternate personalities that don't have to accept it.
有人认为这是种自然反应
Some think it's quite a natural reaction.
艾瑞斯没经历过什么严重外伤
Iris hasn't had any severe traumas.
那场车祸呢
The car accident?
那时我才两岁
I was two.
我什么都不记得
I don't remember anything.
我的这些多重人格...
These personalities that I'm supposed to have...
他们在哪儿呢
Where are they?
只有在你害怕或焦虑的时候他们才出现
They only come out when you're afraid or anxious.
所以豪斯才用了男友受伤的故事
That's why House used the hurt boyfriend story.
但是如果她没有男友
But if there's no boyfriend,
这些伤痕是哪儿来的呢
where did the bruises come from?
还有怀孕呢
The pregnancy?
当你说你男友打了你
When you say your boyfriend hit you,
其实是你自己打了自己
it means you actually hit yourself.
至于怀孕...
And the pregnancy...
并不需要有男友
Doesn't take a boyfriend.
只要有个男生就行
Just a boy.
你可能做了很多事  自己却不知道
You may not be aware of half the things you've done.
为什么她发生了那么大的事
How could this be happening to my own daughter
我却一点也不知情
without me knowing it?
安定掩盖了症状
Diazepam was masking it.
停药后症状凸显出来了
Taking her off made it more apparent.
但是我没有服用
But I--I wasn't on...
安定
"Diazepam"?
那是什么药
What is that?
就是我给你吃的那些维生素
That's what those vitamin pills were.
艾瑞斯  我对不起你
Iris...I am so sorry.
我觉得你有些情绪化
I just, I thought you were moody.
我不想让你感觉你需要药物治疗
I didn't want you to think you needed medication.
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
不敢相信我这么蠢
I can't believe how stupid I've been.
我们需要你帮个忙
We need you to help us with something.
你不同的人格有各自的症状
Different alters can have different apparent symptoms.
有过敏  感觉异常  视力损伤
Allergies, paresthesia, vision loss,
-以及血压波动等  -你认为是我装的
- changes in blood pressure. - Do you think I'm making this up?
你的症状是真实的
Your symptoms are real.
有些是生理上的
But some are physiological,
有些是心理上的
and others are psychological.
这么说除了多重人格之外
So there's something wrong with her...
她还得了别的病吗
in addition to the multiple personalities?
是的  但目前无法下定论
Yes, but we won't know what
需要唤醒其它人格  并对比他们的症状
until we access her alters and compare their symptoms.
这要怎么做到
Well, how do you do that?
用催眠术
Hypnosis.
福曼不会让步的
Foreman's not gonna back down.
他没那么白痴
He's not an idiot.
他就是那么白痴
Yes, he is.
和你一样
Just like you.
如果你继续玩硬的
If you keep being stubborn,
他也会奉陪下去
he will keep being stubborn.
最终你会捅出篓子
Eventually, you will screw something up,
你们俩都吃不了兜着走
which will be bad news for both of you.
但是你们中间只有一个会面临牢狱之灾
But...only one of you will be in prison.
豪斯  这真的不值
It just isn't worth it, House.
好吧
Okay.
是的  先生
Uh, y-yes, sir.
我是说预约去做脊柱按摩
I--yes, I know I told you that I had a chiropractor's appointment,
但是我爆胎了
but, uh, I got a flat.
是啊
I know, right?
所以
So...
别派巡警来抓我哦
You know, don't send out the marines.
我过几分钟就能上路了
I should be back on the road in a few minutes.
好的  再见
Okay, bye.
我是詹姆斯·威尔森医生  县验尸官
Dr. James Wilson, county coroner.
我有几个问题  是关于你孙子德鲁·勒梅茵的
I'd like to ask you about your grandson, Drew Lemaine.
他在你家的时候都干些什么
What did he do when he was here?
他在哪里玩耍  在哪里进餐
Where did he play? What did he eat?
我们就一直看电视
We watched a lot of TV.
还有就是吃饼干
And ate biscuits.
-你让他玩粉笔吗  -没有
- Did you give him sidewalk chalk? - No.
-颜料什么的呢  -没有
- Finger paints? - No!
沙盒呢
A sandbox?
就像我说的
It's like I said.
我们就一直看电视
We watched a lotta TV.
你在等人吗
You expecting someone?
什么
What?
威尔森医生我个毛
Dr. Wilson my ass!
我警告过你  别来烦他  你个混蛋
I told you to leave him alone, you son of a bitch!
冷静
Temper trigger.
我在和谁说话
Who am I talking to now?
没和谁
Nobody.
你总有个名字吧
You must be somebody.
我太渺小
I'm too little.
没人注意我
Nobody sees me.
没人知道我的存在
Nobody knows I'm here.
血压变为140  90
Bp just went to 140 over 90.
怎么了
What is it?
我的手臂
My arms.
你感觉不到手臂吗
You can't feel them?
没关系  我们能治好的
It's okay. We can fix that.
还有哪里疼吗
Do you hurt anywhere else?
现在不疼
Not right now.
但之前会疼吗
But you used to hurt?
我吃草莓的时候
When I ate strawberries.
还有当我回忆起过去
And when I remember...
你记得受伤时的情景吗
Do you remember being hurt?
我记得所有的一切
I remember everything.
宝贝
Baby...
会没事的  宝贝
It's going to be okay, baby.
艾瑞斯
Iris?
你为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you ever tell me?
是我害死了爸爸
It was my fault daddy died.
不是的
Oh, no. No.
是我害的
Yes, it was.
当时我哭得他都没法开车了
I was crying, and he couldn't drive.
都是我的错
It was my fault daddy's...
宝贝  不是的
Oh, no. No, no, honey.
你当时只是个孩子
Yes. You were just a baby.
不是你的错
It wasn't your fault. No, shh.
是我的错
It was my fault.
我很抱歉  妈妈
I'm sorry, mommy.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
她没有流产
It wasn't a miscarriage.
检查表明她还怀着呢
Test shows she's still pregnant.
把没在每个人格都出现的症状划掉
Okay, cross out everything that doesn't appear in every alter.
当她打开预言球的时候
When she opened the magic 8 ball,
触动了一个
that triggered a switch
对草莓过敏的人格
to a personality with a strawberry allergy.
怀孕  阴道出血  高血压
Pregnancy, vaginal bleeding, and elevated B.P.
可能是先兆子痫
Could be pre-eclampsia.
最糟的情况是宫外孕
Worst case, could be an ectopic pregnancy.
我们要做个超声波
We need to ultrasound.
输卵管内未见胚胎
Not seeing an embryo in the fallopian tube.
哪里都没有胚胎
I'm not seeing an embryo anywhere.
哪个白痴做的孕检
Which idiot did the pregnancy test?
一次是我做的  一次是奇斯做的
I did one of them. Chase did another.
后来陶博又检查了一次  三次都是阳性
Taub did a third. Three tests, three positives.
你眼睛怎么了
What happened to your eye?
我摸了朴克的屁股
I grabbed Park's ass.
太阳系外行星
Exoplanets.
他刚刚说太阳系外行星
I think he said exoplanets.
等他说完
Wait for it...
我们实际上看不到它们
We can't actually see them...
却可以推断出它们的存在
but we infer their existence
因为它们对所环绕的恒星会产生一定影响
because of the effect they have on the star they orbit.
孕检只能通过上升的人绒毛膜促性腺激素水平
Pregnancy test only infers an embryo's existence
推断出胎儿的存在
because of  elevated HCG levels.
宫绒毛膜癌同样会引起激素水平上升
Which could also be caused by choriocarcinoma,
并且会影响到激素分泌  造成妊娠假象
which affects the placenta, mimics pregnancy,
并引发血压上升和阴道出血
and causes elevated BP and vaginal bleeding.
隐匿性绒癌
Occult choriocarcinoma,
因此超声波未能显示
which is why we didn't see it on the ultrasound.
告诉她所有的人格
Tell all the alters
他们患了癌症
that they have cancer.
妈妈还是爸爸
Mom or dad?
妈妈  爸爸  还有妈妈的爸爸
Mom, dad, and mom's dad.
好消息是  我终于意识到你是对的
The good news is, made me realize that you were right.
我就是放不下
I can't drop it.
不过在接受了这个事实之后
But now that I accept that,
我心里就不那么矛盾了
I feel much less conflicted.
我已经排除了韦格纳肉芽肿
I've ruled out Wegener's,
比格氏病  重金属中毒
Berger's, heavy metal poison...
两列火车就要相撞
Two trains are about to collide,
而我竟然在劝它们不要相撞
and I'm trying to talk them out of it.
感觉我漏掉了什么
Feels like I'm missing something.
不  不  你不想听我说话
No, no. You don't want to listen to me,
那我也不想听你说
then I don't want to listen to you.
-真是孩子气  -我同意
- That is so fifth grade. - I agree.
知道为什么吗
And you know why?
因为我不比你强
Because I'm just as bad as you.
我明知道你会充耳不闻
I knew this would fall on deaf ears,
可我还是不停地说下去
but I just kept talking and talking.
你说的对
You're right.
你都不知道我刚刚说了什么
You don't even know what I just said.
才怪
That is ridiculous.
你说什么什么耳不闻
You said, "Blah blah blah blah blah, deaf ears,
什么什么
blah blah blah blah blah."
绝对的关键信息
Absolutely essential information.
雷
Ray...
Ray!
离他远点
Leave him alone.
你对他做了什么
What are you doing to him?
没事的
It's okay.
梅姬
Mickey...
是你  你带他来的
You? You brought him.
我请他来这里见我  跟家人聚聚
I asked him to meet me here for a family reunion.
雷
Ray!
我们走吧  好不好
Let's just get out of here, okay?
我知道你儿子的死因
I know what killed your son.
你就是不明白  是不是
You don't get it, do you?
我不在乎他的死因
I don't care what killed him!
奥尔波特综合征
It's called Alport Syndrome.
是一种遗传性疾病  其特征包括肾衰竭
It's a genetic condition characterized by kidney failure,
支气管肌瘤  米氏线和耳聋
bronchial myomas, Mees' lines, and deafness.
白痴  德鲁才不聋
Idiot. Drew wasn't deaf!
-豪斯  -你这混蛋
- House... - Son of a bitch!
离他们远点
Get away from them!
豪斯  豪斯
House, House!
那是遗传病
It's a genetic condition!
-闭嘴  -遗传性的
- Shut up! - Genetic!
你父亲有那种基因
Your father has the gene.
你也有
So do you.
外公的耳背让我猜到了根源
It's grandpa's slight deafness that gave the game away.
你明显是无症状的
You're apparently asymptomatic.
但你还是有可能把基因遗传给你的孩子
You could still pass the gene onto your children.
两个孩子
Plural.
你撒谎
You're lying.
他有高频听力损伤
He has high-frequency hearing impairment.
德鲁也一样
And so did Drew.
所以德鲁才自己造词
That's why Drew made up his own words.
因为他听不清楚
'cause he couldn't hear properly.
不用担心  我们已经清楚了病因
It's okay. Now that we know what it is,
他需要治疗  但是可以活下来
he'll need treatment, but he'll live.
要知道  控制愤怒的课程屡见不鲜
You know, there are platitudes that can help you with that.
我也想他
I miss him too.
她的反应很好
She's responding well.
卡迪用门诊时间来威胁他
Cuddy threatened him with clinic duty.
我以为用监狱来威胁他会有所不同
I thought threatening him with jail would be different.
这么想也不无道理
Not an irrational thought.
我还是要送他回去
I'm still sending him back.
他救了两条人命
He saved two lives.
所以说我再让步已经来不及了
Which means it's too late for me to back down.
我已经别无选择
It's no longer my choice.
否则就等于告诉他  以后可以肆意妄为
It's just me telling him he can get away with anything.
我必须送他回监狱
I have to send him to prison.
你的工作是维持医院的运转
Your job is to keep this machine running.
豪斯是可用之材还是害群之马
It's your choice to make House a useful tool
完全在于你怎样利用
or a monkey wrench.
卡迪能成功领导他
Cuddy's way didn't fail
是因为她没有去控制豪斯
because she didn't try to control House.
而是支配他
She managed him.
她比所有人都更清楚他有时多混蛋
She knew better than anybody what a tool he could be.
卡迪在的话会怎么做
What would Cuddy have done?
十小时门诊
Ten clinic hours.
卡迪不当家了
Cuddy's not here anymore.
三十小时
You got 30.